

#### MASTER STUDENT · COMPUTER VISION · MEDICAL IMAGE PROCESSING

4259 Nagatsuta-cho, Midori-ku Yokohama, Kanagawa 226-8503 Japan

□ (+81) 090-9102-7626 | 🗷 sunhaozju@outlook.com | 🐔 haosun99.xyz | 🖸 SunHao-TokyoTech | 🛅 haosun117/

"Aut Caesar, aut nihil."

## **Summary**

I am currently a master student at Tokyo Institute of Technology, supervised by Prof. Kenji SUZUKI. I received my B.Eng degree from the School of Computer Science and Technology, Zhejiang University in 2021. At that time, I am also a member of Chu Kochen Honors College. During the university, I also minored in Religious Philosophy, Zhejiang University. Now my main research interest lies in medical image processing, dose reduction for CT.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### Fenlai Intelligent Co.,Ltd.

ShenZhen, China

COMPUTER VISION ALGORITHM ENGINEER (INTERNSHIP)

Mar.2021 - Jun.2021

- · Smart gym based on computer vision technology. I am responsible for the overall architecture design and algorithm implementation of the group exercise project, and realize the multi-person real-time group exercise scoring and action correction system.
- Edge deployment of deep learning models and load balancing system.

Hikvision Co.,Ltd. HangZhou, China

COMPUTER VISION ALGORITHM ENGINEER (INTERNSHIP)

Sep.2021 - Oct.2021

Investigate video-based pedestrian re-identification technology.

### **Honors & Awards**

INTERNATIONAL

IIR Research Fellow, Institute of Innovative Research (IIR), Tokyo Institute of Technology 2022

Tokyo, Japan

**DOMESTIC** 

2rd Scholarship, Zhejiang University 2018

HangZhou, China

# Research Project

#### 3D hair modeling from 2D sketches

Zhejiang University CAD/CG Lab

· Given a 3D bust model as reference, our sketching system takes as input a user-drawn sketch (consisting of hair contour and a few strokes indicating the hair growing direction within a hair region), and automatically generates a 3D hair model, matching the input sketch.

## Virtual high dose CT image reconstruction based on paired low dose and high dose CT image

Kenji Suzuki Laboratory

RESEARCHER

2021.12

· Use paired CT images to train Massive Training Artificial Nerual Network to reduce artifacts and noise in low-dose CT images, enhance image

quality, and assist doctors in diagnosis.

#### **Fluorescence Images for Enhancing Proteins**

Kenji Suzuki Laboratory

RESEARCHER

2022.4

· Confidential Project

## **Education**

**ZheJiang University** HangZhou, China

B.ENG IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep. 2017 - Jul.2021

· Selected as a member of Chu Kochen Honors College and won the 2rd scholarship of Zhejiang University.

HAO SUN · RÉSUMÉ **SEPTEMBER 13, 2022** 

## Tokyo Institute of Technology

Tokyo, Japan

Sep. 2021 - Jul.2023

M.ENG IN INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

• Research Fellow from Institute of Innovative Research(IIR)